logoworks.com 2002-12-06

# GET A LOGO AT LOGOWORKS!

Contact webmaster@logoworks.com with questions or problems. 

LogoWorks is owned and operated by Arteis, Inc. When you're visiting the LogoWorks site, we don't want you to worry that we will misuse the information you share with us about yourself. It is important to us that all of our customers understand what information we gather about them, how we use it, and how we work to protect it. By using the LogoWorks service and this website, you consent to the information practices described in this policy. Keep in mind that your use of the LogoWorks service is also subject to, and controlled by, the LogoWorks Customer Agreement. 

Information Collection 

  * Personally Identifiable Information is information that can be used to locate you, contact you, or determine your specific identity. When other information is linked to Personally Identifiable Information, it also becomes Personally Identifiable Information. 
  * LogoWorks collects Personally Identifiable Information from you in several ways: 
    1. When you register for the LogoWorks Service, we ask you for basic registration information, such as your name, company, address, email address, phone, fax, and other basic contact information ("Registration Information"). 
    2. When you place an order or subscribe to a product through the LogoWorks service, we may collect the appropriate billing information, including your credit card number, expiration date, and billing address ("Billing Information"). This information is associated with your Registration Information in a database and will be kept for future purchases. 
    3. We may ask you for voluntary personal information at other times, including but not limited to when you provide opinions, enter a contest or promotion, or report a problem with the LogoWorks service ("Optional Information"). 
    4. When you submit a request for more information or assistance, LogoWorks will keep a record of the request and the manner in which it was processed ("Customer Service Information"). 

  * In addition to the collection of Personally Identifiable Information, we may also automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, your computer's name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses, and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information. 
  * While using the LogoWorks reader to access or review a particular design project ("LogoWorks Reader"), the reader software will record the date and time that you reviewed the design works. Such information will not be associated with Personally Identifiable Information ("Reader Information"). 

Limits on Information Collection 

  * By default, the LogoWorks Reader will record the non-personally identifiable Reader Information described above. If you do not want LogoWorks to have this type of information, you may change a setting in the options area of the LogoWorks Reader and prevent any information from being sent to LogoWorks. 
  * We must have your Personally Identifiable Information in order for us to adequately provide you with the LogoWorks service. 
  * Note that by limiting information collection, LogoWorks may not be able to provide you the same functionality or features as otherwise available (if such functionality or features rely on this information). 

Cookies 

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookies to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) most browsers only permit a web site to access the cookies that the same web site has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 
  * LogoWorks may set and access our own cookies on your computer. LogoWorks may use cookies to identify you as a repeat visitor or customer of the website, to maintain session information for logged in users, and to track usage trends and patterns in order to better understand and improve areas of our website. 
  * LogoWorks may also allow other companies or individuals that are presenting content on our site to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of cookies is subject to their own respective privacy policies. We do not have access to any information stored by third party advertisers about you. 

Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information   
In general, we will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent. If we seek your consent to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to a third party, we will do so unambiguously, explaining precisely what information we seek to disclose, the entity to whom we wish to disclose it, and the purpose for the disclosure. 

There are, however, some limited circumstances in which we may be need to disclose Personally Identifiable Information about a user, and we want you to know about them: 

  * We may employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, providing customer service, sending mail, processing credit card payments, or other functions necessary to our business. We may need to share your Personally Identifiable Information to these companies. However, we will provide them with only that information necessary to perform their functions, and will not allow them to use that information for any other purpose. 
  * Authors of the products you purchase or subscribe to through the LogoWorks service may request additional Personally Identifying Information from you. LogoWorks will provide the authors of such products the information you supply in response to those requests. The information practices of those publishers are not covered by this privacy policy. 
  * We may reveal a user's identity (or whatever information we know about that individual) if we believe that user is harming or interfering with other LogoWorks users, anyone else, or violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Customer Agreement or infringing any of LogoWorks's legal rights. 
  * LogoWorks will reveal information, including Personally Identifiable Information, to the extent it reasonably believes it is required to do so by law. If we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of any of your personally identifiable information we will, if permitted by law, attempt to notify you via the e-mail address you supplied during registration within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request. 
  * LogoWorks may transfer information it collects, including any Personally Identifiable Information, in connection with a sale of all or most of the assets of the company. 

Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information 

  * Anonymous Information is any information collected from you or by the LogoWorks service, other than Personally Identifiable Information, including aggregate information derived from Personally Identifiable Information. 
  * LogoWorks may use Anonymous Information to improve the LogoWorks website and service, to monitor traffic and general usage patterns, and for other general business purposes. 
  * LogoWorks may disclose Anonymous Information to third parties for a variety of business reasons, including to publishers to inform them as to what content is appealing to their readers, to advertisers to inform them of the usage habits or characteristics of the interested audience, and to potential investors so that they may better understand LogoWorks's user base, etc. 
  * Anonymous Information will not include any Personally Identifiable Information and LogoWorks will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information except as expressly stated elsewhere in this policy. 

Changing or Removing Information 

  * LogoWorks wants to ensure that you have appropriate control over your Personally Identifiable Information. You can change your Registration or Customer Information, by clicking here. 
  * If at any time you would like to delete your Registration Billing Information you can send an e-mail request to support@logoworks.com. After receiving your request, such information will be deleted assuming (i) you are current with all payment obligations; (ii) LogoWorks does not believe it is reasonably necessary to keep such information for any pending legal action; and (iii) we are under no other legal obligation to retain such information. If such information is deleted, however, any unfulfilled subscriptions will be canceled without refund and you will have to re-register with LogoWorks in order to use the LogoWorks service. 
  * Since Anonymous Information is by its very nature non-personally identifying, we have no way to locate Anonymous Information obtained by your use of the service. In addition, Anonymous Information is often aggregated. Therefore, we cannot remove Anonymous Information obtained from you or as a result of your usage of the website or service. 

Security 

  * We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. 
  * Your personal data will be stored within a database that is located behind a firewall for added security. The server housing the database is physically protected at a secure, third party site and is monitored by security personnel twenty-four hours a day. Only authorized personnel can access the data center and the particular server housing the database. 
  * No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 
  * We do not encrypt your normal web sessions with the Service using SSL. Any transmission to the LogoWorks website or service of credit card information uses SSL encryption. 

Children 

  * The LogoWorks service is not directed to children (persons under the age of 13), and we do not knowingly collect, either online or offline, personally identifiable information from children. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

* From time to time, LogoWorks may change its privacy policy. If we make any changes regarding disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, then we'll send you an e-mail (or notify you by pop-up screen) prior to the date the modified policy takes effect. We will also post conspicuous notice of the new policy on our home page. Any new policy will have prospective effect only, meaning it will not apply to information previously gathered without your express consent. Questions 

  * If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or our use of your information, please email support@logoworks.com.
